<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Your First Rails Project">
  <intro>
    <description>A cheat sheet which demonstrates generating a Rails project, setting up the configuration and generating a resource.</description>
  </intro>

	<item title="Open the Rails perspective">
		<command
			serialization="org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective(org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective.perspectiveId=org.radrails.rails.ui.PerspectiveRails)"
			confirm="true">
		</command>
		<description>
			If you're not already in the Rails perspective, in the main menu
			select <b>Window</b> &gt; <b>Open Perspective</b> &gt; <b>Rails</b>
			or click on the &quot;Click to Perform&quot; link below.
		</description>
	</item>

  	<item
		title="Create a Rails project"
		dialog="true">
		<command
			serialization="org.eclipse.ui.newWizard(newWizardId=org.radrails.rails.ui.wizards.NewWizardProject)"
			confirm="true">
		</command>
		<description>
			In the main toolbar, click on the <b>New Rails Project</b> button, or click on
			the link below. Enter <b>rails</b> for the project name, then
			click <b>Finish</b>.
		</description>
	</item> 

	<item title="Rails project generation output">
		<description>
			As the rails command is run to generate your project, you should see the <b>Rails Shell</b> appear in the <b>Console</b> view.
            <br/>
			<br/>
            This view will show the output of the <b>rails</b> command and creates hyperlinks for the generated files. You can use those links to quickly open the files.
            <br/>
			<br/>
            Additionally this view is an alternate way of entering rails related commands in a shell/console fashion - including the ability to 
            run the <b>rails</b> command to generate rails projects.
		</description>
	</item> 

	<item title="Open the database.yml file">
		<description>
			Now that you have your Rails project, you'll want to edit/verify your database connection settings.
			<br/>
			<br/>
			Click the link for <b>config/database.yml</b> in the <b>Rails Shell</b> (you'll likely need to scroll up), 
			or expand the project in the <b>Ruby Explorer</b> and double-click the file.
		</description>
	</item>

	<item title="Edit/Verify your database settings">
		<description>
			Edit and/or verify your database settings. <br/>
			<br/>
			If you are using sqlite, there's not much to do.<br/>
			<br/>
			With other databases you'll want to enter the username, password, host and port information. You'll also need to manually create the database outside RadRails.			
		</description>
	</item>
  
</cheatsheet>
